The true kinda love.
Steven Universe: The Movie is a tv movie, adventure,
animation film directed by Rebecca Sugar.
Two years after bringing peace to the galaxy, Steven Universe sees his past come back to
haunt him in the form of a deranged Gem who wants to destroy the Earth.
Steven Universe (voice), played by Zach Callison.
Pearl / Yellow Pearl (voice), played by Deedee Magno.
Garnet (voice), played by Estelle.
Amethyst (voice), played by Michaela Dietz.
Spinel (voice), played by Sarah Stiles.
Greg Universe (voice), played by Tom Scharpling.
Steven Universe: The Movie is a 2019 American animated musical science fantasy television film and a sequel to the
television series of the same name, taking place two years after the series finale "Change Your Mind".
Directed and co-written by series creator Rebecca Sugar with co-direction by Joe Johnston and Kat Morris, the film stars Zach
Callison, Estelle, Michaela Dietz, and Deedee Magno Hall returning from the series, joined by Sarah Stiles.
Its plot follows the Crystal Gems as they attempt to save all organic life on
Earth from a deranged Gem with a history with Steven's mother.
The film was announced at San Diego Comic-Con 2018, and a short teaser
trailer was later released on Cartoon Network's YouTube channel.
At San Diego Comic-Con 2019, an official trailer was released, along with the
announcement of a making-of documentary bundled with the film's DVD.
The film premiered on Cartoon Network on September
2, 2019, to 1.57 million viewers.
It was the first Cartoon Network original film
since Regular Show: The Movie (2015).
The film was followed by the epilogue limited series
Steven Universe Future (2019–2020).
The film explores themes of musical, memory loss,
abandonment, vengeance, abandonment issues.
The tone is emotional and thought_provoking.